Max!
Come here.
Let's not make the sisters wait.
Her name is Frey.
She's new here too.
Can you read?
This is a giraffe. They lived in Africa.
You can read?
Yes.
There are many robot servers, and they serve you all day.
If you live there, you'll never get sick, or old.
I'll take us there, one day.
-Really?     -Yes, I promise.
Frey and Max.
Forever.
Max, are you stealing again?
It breaks my heart. Why do you do it?
To save up ?
You want to buy a ticket to go up there?
That place is not for you, or me.
It's not fair, sister.
Why can't I go?
There are things in life that can't be explained.
We just have to accept them.
But one thing I know for sure.
You're a very special person.
One day you'll do something marvellous.
You were born for it.
My little Max.
Max, muy bueno!
Off to work, huh? Gotta get up early, to work that line.
Wanna make the world a better place?
That's real funny, I have a job. Chistoso.
Por favor ninos! You think I got money?
Do I look like I have money?
How about you, you got a little money?
Come on, whatta you got in there?
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's 5 bucks. Hey, wait a minute. I got 5 bucks, I'm rich.
I can buy my ticket to Elysium, huh?
Alright.
Please form an orderly queue. Your bus has arrived.
I don't have anything.
Checked. Move on.
Morning, Officer.
Extensive criminal history. Multiple felonies. What's in the bag?
Hair products, mostly.
I'm just fucking with...
Hey... I'm just going to work, man. There's nothing in the fucking bag.
Come on, I...
Misdemeanor: citizen disobedience.
Just going to work, man. Come on.
-Checked.     -Nothing in there, is it?
Zero-tolerance policy applies to all citizens.
No shit?
You must report immediately to your parole officer.
Thank you, Citizen.
No, thank you.
Frey, fracture in bed 2.
Max?
Frey...
I thought you were...
-When did you get back?     -Been back for a while.
-I see things haven't changed.     -No, this wasn't even my fault.
Of course not.
-Let me have a look.     -How is it?
Pretty bad break.
So you're a nurse, huh? You did it!
Yeah.
That's great.
You still stealing cars?
No, God, I don't do any of that stupid shit anymore.
I work at Armadyne. On the line, you know? Working...
-Frey, they need you up on the 3rd floor.     -Be right there.
-So, you know, now that you're back...     -Just a second.
Just a second.
Dominica, can you take over here?
Hey, listen. Now, you know, 'cause you're back and everything.
Max, I'm so sorry I have to go.
It's good to see you. Stay out of trouble.
I do.
Look...
I know why you left the neighborhood, I understand.
If I was as smart as you I would have left too.
Have dinner with me. Just...
I'll settle for a coffee.
-No.     -Aww.
Have I gotta break my other arm to get attention?
-Stop.     -...'cause I will do that.
My life is complicated, Max.
I just, I... I miss you.
-My shift ends at 8 on Wednesday, OK?     -Yeah, all right.
-Coffee.     -Yeah, coffee. Right.
Get out of here.
All parolees must have weapons inspection
Hello.
Before we start, I'd just like to explain...
Max da Costa, violation of Penal Code 2219. Today at bus stop 34-B.
Yes, that's exactly what I wanted to talk to you about.
See I believe there's been a misunderstanding.
Immediate extension of parole by a further 8 months.
Wait, What? No, no, I can explain what happened.
I just made a joke. And, you know...
Stop talking.
Police officers noted violent and antisocial behavior.
We regrettably must extend parole.
Elevation in heart rate detected.
-Would you like a pill?     -No!
Thank you, what I'd like to do is expl...
Stop talking.
Personality matrix suggests a 78.3% chance of regression to old behavior patterns.
Grand theft auto, assault with a deadly weapon,
resisting arrest.
-Would you like to talk to a human?     -No, I am OK. Thank you.
-Are you being sarcastic and/or abusive?     -Negative.
It is a federal offense to abuse a Parole Officer.
Understood.
Hey, da Costa!
-You're late for your shift.     -Yeah man, I had a little thing...
No, no. You can't work with that. You're out.
No, no, I'm good, man. I can work.
It's coming off later today. I'm fine.
-You're good?     -I'm good!
OK, I'm docking you half a day.
-Yeah, alright.     -You're lucky to have this job.
No weapons detected. You are clear for entry.
Please keep your workstation tidy.
A tidy workstation is an efficient workstation.
Hey check it out, man. I think he likes you.
Think he got his face peeled today? He looks good.
Attention: all workers must reach weekly quotas.
Please report any unsafe activity to your supervisor.
If we don't have a clear path to up-side,
our investors are going to start losing a lot of confidence.
What do you think I've been doing here, on Earth?
D'you think I enjoy breathing this air?
-No, of course, but...     -I'm doing everything possible...
to restore profitability to this company.
The company that I built.
Now, if you will excuse me,
I have to not speak to you people any longer. Thank you.
Closing 34!
Firing 34.
Tag her, quick!
Let's go, we don't have much time.
We have 3 transporter codes, Spider.
OK, pull'em up on screen.
Codes have been accepted.
Fire up the shuttles!
We're going up!
-Welcome.     -Hello, ma'am.
-Take a look at the garden.     -We will, thank you.
-Hello, Madame Delacourt.     -Hello.
Hi, Ivan, how you've grown.
Hi. You alright?
-Fine. Are the kids here?     -Yes, with Dominica.
I have a present for you. Wanna see? It's in the salon.
Go get it with your mother.
-It's, by the canape.     -OK
Bye.
Ma'am, would you care for a refreshment?
Demand's cancelled.
Sorry for disturbing you, ma'am. We have a number of undocumented ships inbound.
Good afternoon, Defense Secretary Delacourt.
3 undocumented ships are approaching Elysium airspace.
Emergency orders 6 and 7 are now in effect.
Protocol 22/B39...
Attention, incoming vessels.
You have made unauthorized entry into Elysium airspace.
-Dad!     -It's OK!
We will be forced to take immediate action.
You are in violation of Elysium airspace.
Standard warning didn't work.
15,000 kilometers and closing...
-What do you want us to do, ma'am?     -Activate Kruger.
Ma'am, according to Executive Order 355 we are unauthorized to use our assets on earth
I am authorizing you.
Yes, ma'am.
Agent 32--over. We are sending the packet--over.
Welcome, Agent Kruger!
10,000 kilometers and closing.
Sending coordinates to asset.
Three target data.
Shoot them down!
Green light, 21-B. Green light.
Missiles away!
Shit.
Impacto inminente. 10...
8... 7... 6...
5... 4... 3...
2... 1...
Two ships destroyed. 46 total casualties.
Impact in 5...
-Last missile was a miss.     -Ridiculous!
Only one made it.
Ma'am, the ship has breached our atmosphere.
First undocumented ship just touched down.
I want everyone coming out of that vehicle apprehendeded.
Identification confirmed.
Scanning.
Reconstruction process initiating.
No!
We have 32 arrests, 13 casualties, and 2 illegals at large, Ma'am.
Reconstruction complete.
You are under arrest, under the 68-C Immigration Act.
-All illegals are now in custody, ma'am.     -Yes.
Send them to deportation, Get them off this habitat.
Secretary Delacourt, please report to President Patel immediately.
Secretary Delacourt, report to President Patel.
What up, man? ?que te paso?
Lo es siempre, the police, man.
-Are you OK?     -Yeah, don't worry about it.
Max, I gotta talk to you. You know...
-No!     -What do you mean no?
You didn't even hear what I was gonna say.
-Alright, go ahead.     -OK.
You know the house of Doseta's up on the hill?
Yeah, the one with all the guns.
Yeah, they have five cars. New ones.
It's gonna be three of us. Tomorrow, at lunch.
-Lunch time?     -That's the plan?
Jesus Christ.
-You have a better plan?     -Yeah, just take one guy.
Go before the sun comes up. You take the two fastest cars.
Torch the batteries on the other ones.
Fuck you. Fuck you!
I got you, cojone!
Oh please. You're the best. Give me one year.
-I'm not going back to prison.     -One year, please!
Look at you! You used to be a legend, and now what?
The time is 5:50 am.
No weapons detected. You are clear for entry.
Closing 34!
Attention, doors are not aligned. Worker attend.
Hey, you're holding up the line.
No, no, I got a jam!
Attention: workers may not use the restroom more than once per sh...
-What've you done, da Costa?     -No, I'm just trying to reset.
Let me look.
-The pallet's pinched.     -Yeah, It didn't move.
-Just go in there.     -No, I mean...
Look, you go in there right now...
or we'll find someone who will, and you can go clean out your locker.
-Come on, man.     -No, no. That's the deal, OK?
In you go!
Let's go, people, back to work!
Fuck.
No, no, no, stop!
Hey!
Hey, come on, vamos!
Too late!
Extraction!
Sister, they beat me up.
I only want to live there.
See how beautiful it looks to us down here?
Yes.
Well, now...
See how beautiful we look to them up there.
Keep this.
Now it belongs to you.
So you never forget where you come from.
What happened?
You have been exposed to a lethal dose of radiation.
You will experience catastrophic organ failure.
In five days time, you will die.
What is going on? Why has production stopped?
-He's been exposed ...     -Don't breathe on me.
-Cover your mouth.     -I'm sorry, sir.
Does his skin fall off, or something?
I don't want to replace the bedding in there. Just get him out.
-Yes, sir.     -Right, thank you.
Mr. Carlyle, your shuttle is ready for departure.
Please sign this to receive medication.
Miporol--extremely potent.
Will keep you functioning normally until your death.
Please take one pill with each meal.
Thank you for your service.
At 15:00 hours yesterday you shot down two shuttles, killing 46 civilians.
Your mandate is to deal with illegals 'quietly'.
I am aware of that.
And then there's the use of this... agent.
A Mr. M. Kruger.
15 human rights violations...
Rapes, kidnappings, torture.
The man's been diagnosed with serious psychological issues.
We made it explicitly clear to you that we're no longer using sleeper agents.
Tell me something, President Patel.
Do you have children?
I'm not the one being reviewed here.
Then I will assume you do not.
Perhaps, if you did have children,
then you would behave in a manner
that is more conducive to the longevity of this habitat.
I understand, it is not the fashion to think and to act as I do.
I understand that perfectly.
But when they come for your house...
or the house you built for your children,..
and your children's children...
It won't be PR and campaign promises that keep them out.
It will be me!
I've heard enough! This is your final warning.
Any further unauthorized actions, and you will be removed from office.
And let's discharge this agent Kruger permanently.
All in favour?
Good. Effective immediately.
You want some beer?
You have been discharged from CCB.
Please return all weapons to local embassy.
Fuck your 'Politikster'! Fuck you!
Look...
Max...
Max!
What's wrong? What happened?
Jesus, let me help you. Let's go.
Max, what happened?
-Max, what happened?     -I shouldn't have gone in, man.
Gone in where?
I took a full dose, man.
A full dose.
You're gonna be OK. Let me help.
-You're gonna be OK, Max.     -They gave me Miporol, man.
They gave me... Miporol.
I got five fucking days! I only got five days!
You have to take this.
-They can fix this shit on Elysium, man.     -I know.
-I'm gonna go see Spider.     -Max, Max!
Take the pill!
There you go!
To see Spider, you need money.
I'll give you everything I have, but it's not enough for a ticket.
He's going to give me a ticket.
He's gonna give me a fucking ticket.
Frey, you know we've done everything we could to help your daughter.
But I had a meeting today with the board,
and they're recommending that we send her home with you.
How can I work here and leave her at home?
You know it can happen any minute, Dr. Faizel.
I know, if she has another seizure, of course bring her back here.
But until then she's discharged.
This isn't Elysium. We can't just heal her.
Max!
It's been a while, my brother!
How's life at the factory?
-I need to ask you a favour.     -What? I can't hear you. What?
I need a ticket. Up there. And an ID.
Yeah, sure sure.
Absolutely. You prefer aisle or window?
I'm being fucking serious, man.
Listen, I'm gonna come back and work for you.
Anything you need. I'll fucking pay it back.
You know what?
This... is...
priceless.
This is priceless.
Yeah, let me ask you a question.
Do you have any idea how many idiots
come in here saying the same kinda bullshit?
I got little kids coming here every day.
Max, if I were you, I'd get the fuck out of here, right now
Max, No...
I did 3 years for you.
Everything I did for you, you're gonna get me up there.
-Can you feel this?     -Go ahead and shoot.
I got so much radiation in my body right now,
you're probably getting a little sick yourself.
-You really dying?     -I'm fucking dying, motherfucker.
See this? It's over. I put the gun down.
Put the gun down! Put the gun down! Get out of here!
OK!
Listen, I've been looking for someone to take a job for me.
But no one here had the balls.
You said you'd do anything, right?
Max...
-OK.     -I'm OK.
This...
my friend,
this can be your ticket up there.
One last job for me, you earn your way up.
What is it?
Take an Elysian asshole, right?
A billionaire who's down on Earth for some business...
He's, he's here for, whatever. We hijack him.
-Fuck that!     -Relax.
The guy's like much worse.
Forget his watch, forget his ride, forget all that shit.
This, is what you take.
Organic Information, right out of his head.
I'm talking about bank codes, passwords, login data...
Access to billions.
All you have to do is plug into his brain, download the data to yours with this baby,
and bring it to me.
This is crazy, Max.
Once we verify the data, I'll give you a one way ride, all expenses paid.
Even throw in some snacks and a drink.
All you have to do is walk into a house and use the med-bay, and you're cured.
Sandro will do the surgery. You know him?
-Fuck...     -Christ!
I'm good.
Actually, you seem all weak.
And fucked up, so...
You know what? I have...
This is crazy, let's get out of here, Please, listen to me.
What the fuck am I gonna do?
I'll have them install...
...this!
A third generation Axo-suit.
We hook this into your nerval system, and it'll make you as strong as a droid.
You're already under the knife, right?
Let's get out of here, please.
I want a 4 man team. But I pick them.
I'm sending my own data wrangler.
Brain to brain, that is real tough.
OK, but I'm taking Julio. He gets a ticket up there, same as me.
Yeah, sure.
OK, I'll go get the boys ready.
Wait!
It's gotta be John Carlyle.
The CEO of Armadyne, Carlyle?
That's the mark.
Secretary Delacourt, Mr. Carlyle has arrived.
You are here to persuade me to renew our Armadyne contracts, yes?
Astute as always.
Come with me.
I'm not interested in your little ideas.
I am interested in something much larger.
This habitat is dying.
There is a political sickness inside of it. A tumor that needs to be removed.
You and your company are in need of revenue that is drying up.
So...
You built the Torus.
Can you override the servers and place a new president in power?
A coup?
Are you suggesting a coup?
Is it possible?
I could write a reboot sequence.
It'd shut down the entire system, and at that point...
you can encode a new President, yes.
Then that is what you will do.
And you will have your contract secured for the next 200 years.
Missile Defense Batteries, Droids, everything we need, to protect our liberty.
all guaranteed, of course, by your new President.
Go! Get to work, Mr. Carlyle.
This is the guy.
-He's the guy?     -This is him.
Sit down.
We're gonna cut you up good, homie.
Play nice, amigo. Play nice.
Let's get him an ID first.
Give the chief one of my identification codes.
Get that ready.
Arm up.
Weonly have
What did you find?
And we'll merge it with the DNA. Now you fit in.
Like you were born there.
Now it's time for the real fun.
Hey, man.
Yo.
This gonna hurt?
Yeah bitch, it's gonna hurt.
It's gonna hurt good.
When we're done with you, you're gonna be a  ninja.
Mariana!...
Bring down the bone saw!
This ain't gonna kill me.
You'll be airight. Not bad.
Max.
I'm here.
We got this, man.
We got this?
Yeah!
Hey!
He's awake!
Made it, huh?
Surprise!
You can still jack off, alright?
How's everything going?
Ready to kick ass?
What the fuck did you do to me?
Gave you a way out.
Shit.
What's up, partner?
How's that suit working out for you?
That shit is tight!
Show me.
Hold this.
Is it a family heirloom?
Wait for it.
Air-bursting ammunition.
Designate your enemy...
and any round you fire will explode around a 5 meter kill radius.
And...
safe detonation rounds for this bad boy.
That'll work.
Move out!
Sir...
Your shuttle is ready.
Do you read me?
Yes.
Alright, here's the deal.
We'll wait outside the factory until we see the shuttle leave.
One of you opens an explosive round in it,
goes to the crash site and gets the data.
OK, copy that.
Alright now, let's go! Let's play ball!
You nervous?
-No.     -No?
I'm shitting myself with fear.
-I'm not gonna fucking die.     -No.
Go, go, go!
Acceleration to supersonic speed in 15 seconds.
Come on, come on, come on!
Critical engine failure.
Ma'am, we have an Elysium citizen on Earth in danger.
Data coming up now...
Citizen identified. John Carlyle. N8321...
I see you, motherfucker!
I have a situation here.
Kruger, do you read me?
Ah, Ms Delacourt. How lovely to hear your voice.
There's a citizen carrying sensitive brain data out of the city right now.
Some thieves are trying to hijack it.
What's in it?
That's classified.
You don't call a recently deactivated agent to retreive classified fucking information!
The government doesn't know about this, do they?
I can ask for whatever I want, can't I?
Please brace for impact
Please remain calm. You have sustained zero injuries.
Oh, that's a real comfort.
I've got one condition. I do this, I get re-instated.
Fine.
I've recommissioned 2 of your preferred agents.
Completely confidentially, of course. They should be at your position any second.
Send me the mission data.
Let's go, guys. Out of the cars!
Droids, there appears to be some type of wheeled vehicle, with one
Two occupants.
They are armed and I'd like them dead.
Droid!
It's jammed!
Identified, Max da Costa. Federal Parole number 61492-8-557.
It's jammed, man!
Got it!
He's reloading!
-Guys! We got the bastard!     -Go! I got you covered!
Go, go, go!
Don't fucking move.
Bring it!
There's another one!
Die, motherfucker!
Don't hit the mark!
No, no! He got hit!
Citizen has sustained a cardio-thoracic trauma.
Blood pressure is dropping.
-It's not in the head!     -Is he breathing?
-No, it's in the chest!     -Well, fucking good, man.
Hold his head, hold his head.
Let me see your brain.
Come on, Come on!
-Yes.     -Is it working?
Yeah, we're syncing.
You have no idea what you're doing.
One minute to target, sir.
We're syncing. Come on, baby, here we go.
It's gonna work. We got it.
It's a data heist, ma'am. They're downloading now.
Guys, we've got incoming.
Fuck me!
Come on, guys, hurry up.
That's a Raven. That's Military.
-Alright we got this, 97...98!     -Hurry up, they're coming.
-Almost there!     -99!
In! Here we go!
Shit! Data must be corrupted!
Wait. Hold on.
I can't read the data. It's scrambled! I can't read the data.
What?
-Come on, guys! We gotta move!     -What the fuck does 'scrambled' mean?
Fuck this!
No, No! Run it again! Run it another time!
-Get off me, man! I'm bailing!     -Please. Run it again.
Fuck you! Let's get out of here.
Where the fuck are you going, Sandro?
Let's get outta here! Goddamit!
C'mon man.
Get out of there! Let's go!
We gotta go! Come on! Come on!
Hey, boss, we got a runner.
Fire!
That's what I'm talking about!
Fuck, man!
Target moving south-southwest.
Move back! It's coming!
We got another one.
Again!
This is wrong! This is all wrong, man!
Going into holding pattern, sir!
Where do you think you're going?
Come on!
Fuck!
Motherfucker!
Come on!
No!
No, no!
No! Get up!
Get up!
No!
We've got one assailant leaving on foot, ma'am.
They have the data. Repeat:
The thieves have the data.
Apprehend the target at all costs. Do not damage his brain.
Let's go! We got a runner, boys!
The citizen has suffered catastrophic blood loss leading to cardiac arrest.
Time of death, 17:45.
Come on, where are you hiding?
What's that?
Looks like a herd of pigs, boss.
Fuck you, man! Find him!
Take us back to the crash site, to see what they left behind.
Roger, that.
Thanks.
Hey boss, I think you better come look at this.
This is a record of what we picked up
being transferred between Carlyle and the criminals.
That's why she wants it so badly.
He's got the keys to the kingdom in his fucking head!
Now we just need to find him.
Gonna let the girls out.
Searching grids 3 through 11.
I'm authorising a Full Containment Order.
Issue a No Fly Zone for Los Angeles.
-All of Los Angeles?     -The murderer's still out there.
Until we apprehend him, no one leaves the surface of that city.
What the f...?
Max.
-Hey, sweety!     -Hey.
We can go home.
Am I better?
I'm gonna get the car, OK?
Be right back.
Frey...
Max!
My God, what happened to you?
-Shit, I'm gonna get the medics.     -No, no!
-I can't go in there.     -Max!
-I can't go in...     -Max, listen, you need a doctor, OK?
People are looking for me. They're gonna kill me.
-I came here for you. I need your help.     -Max!
You've got to go through the system to get treatment.
Please help me. I don't wanna die.
Max!
Stay awake!
-I wanna see the man.     -Mama's gonna help him, OK?
Try and sleep.
Don't sleep!
You're too heavy for me. Max, help me!
Come on!
Max, you can do it, come on!
No, wait. Let's turn you over!
Max, Max, wait.
-Thank you.     -Who did this to you?
I don't know. I got-I got hurt at at work.
I had to take a job from Spider to try to get up there and get healed.
It went bad, now I'm in trouble.
Mommy?
Hey, sweety, come here!
Who is that man?
His name is Max. Mommy knew him when he was your age.
-It's Matilda.     -Hi!
You can go watch cartoons, OK?
I'll be right there.
I didn't know you had... I'm so sorry, I need to go.
-Wait, Max, you can not leave.     -I shouldn't have come here. I have to leave!
Max! She's dying. She's in the final stages of leukemia.
I told you my life complicated. I need you to help me.
-I've no idea how to do this.     -How to do what?
-Get her to Elysium.     -I can't help her. I...
I would if I could.
How about this? Fake citizenship. If you took her there,
-could you heal her with this?     -It doesn't work that way.
This is coded to me, it's locked to my DNA.
The people looking for me. They... You don't understand who these people are.
If they find me here, they will kill all of us.
The only thing I can do to help you is leave. I promise you.
-She's all I have.     -I'm sorry.
You have bandages.
Yeah. I got bandages.
What are you doing?
I don't want you to be sick. You wanna hear a story?
N.., ah...
There once was a meerkat who lived in the jungle.
He was hungry and he was small.
So small.
And the other big animals had all the food, 'cause they could reach the fruits.
So he made friends with a hippopotamus
OK, stop!
It doesn't end well for the meerkat.
Yes, it does 'cause he can stand on the hippopotamus' back
to get all the fruits that he wants.
-What's in it for the hippo?     -The hippo wants a friend.
I'm sorry.
Hey, boss.
I think we got him.
Yank this fucking cunt!
-Mommy, is everything OK?     -It's OK, sweety.
Clear!
What is this?
Good afternoon.
Sorry to come bursting into your home. Didn't mean to...
traumatize your young daughter.
Me and the boys here are looking for a young gentleman...
who was in this very house a moment ago.
We're hoping you can tell us where he went.
No.
I...
-I don't know where he is.     -I don't believe in ...
...committing violent acts in front of the kids.
So I just need you to close your eyes, sweetheart.
-It's OK.     -I really need you to tell me.
Hey?
-You remember now?     -Mommy!
Close your eyes, keep your fucking eyes closed.
Keep her eyes closed.
Please, I don't know where he is.
He was wounded, I helped him and he left.
Please!
D'you fucking hear that? No loyalty nowadays, hey?
What's this here?
-This a hospital you're running here?     -She's sick.
She's sick? Let me have a look at her... Alright!
-Don't touch her.     -See that? Protective instinct, here!
I said don't touch her!
I'm just trying to get a word with your child.
Don't touch her!
-Bring her. Come!     -Where are you taking her?
-Now I've got something you want.     -Sweety, it's OK.
It's OK, darling. It's OK.
Sit down! Shut up!
Stop!
No, no, don't shoot him! Put the gun down! Let him come!
-You got something, didn't you?     -What?
That's why they shut down the sky... what is it?
Wire transfers? Corporate intel? You gotta have something big in there!
No. I fucking got nothing, man!
It all got scrambled. Julio is dead. You owe me. Let's go fucking now!
We can't! The flight system is jammed!
Nobody is going up there.
-Until when?     -Till I don't fucking know.
-I gotta fucking get up there!     -Everyone needs to get up there.
My guys are working on it.
See if they have a hope in hell of ever getting back online.
But, for now...
Let's just take a look at that head of yours.
Get away from me, man!
Look at me, if they shut down the whole fucking sky,
for what's in your head...
Maybe the key to opening it could be in there too, right?
Come on.
Alright.
They will hunt you to the edge of the world for this.
What is it?
It's a reboot program for Elysium.
Whoever has this, has the power to override their whole system.
Open the borders...
Make everyone a citizen of Elysium.
This can save your life.
-We can save everyone.     -When can I go?
They're trying to hack through the signal jam, but soon...
-Don't bullshit me, when can we go?     -I dunno.
Five days... a week?
Fuck you, I don't have 5 days! I got hours.
My guys are working on it.
You're always working on it, You can't get me up there.
I don't know why you try sending people up there,
they just get fucking shot down.
Not with what's in your head! That's what I'm talking about!
We would control the system. We would be in charge!
We can change the course of fucking history!
Back up then.
What I have in my head, is worth a lot to them, right?
Don't do this.
If that falls into the wrong hands, they could shut us out for good.
Listen, man, I'm going up there right now.
If you can find me, and I'm healed, you can have all of this.
-But I'm not fucking dying.     -This is wrong, Max, don't do this.
Don't shoot him! Don't shoot him!
It's OK. It's OK.
I always wanted a wife.
Just couldn't quite settle down, you know? Too much temptation.
But you...
You make me ready to settle down.
You really make me want to settle down, baby.
-Holy shit, sir.     -Eh?
You better come take a look at this.
-What is it?     -Check this fucking oak.
Turn us around.
-Take it.     -Right, sir.
Open the door.
Stop right there, and you're gonna do exactly what I say.
Or I'm gonna blow my fucking head off, you understand?
Yeah!
You can have everything in my head!
Just take me up there, and get me in a med-bay.
-What I have is very valuable.     -We can fix you up.
Put you in a med-bay, Sort all this cock-up.
Let's go! We'll take you up there.
Weather's nice, air's nice and clean. Likely you'll dig it.
-Don't you fucking try anything!     -Step aboard!
Come meet the boys, come on!
Don't be shy, they won't bite.
Let me introduce you. This is Drakie. This is Max.
What is news?
Let's fly!
Yes, ma'am, we apprehended the subject.
-Open the skies, we're coming up.     -I'll expect you in 19 minutes.
-Cancel the No Fly Zone.     -Yes, ma'am.
Hold it...
Hold it. What is that? ...
Are we back? Marcelo! What the fuck is that? Are we back?
We're back online, Spider.
Frey...
I'm sorry. I'm gonna make this right.
-We've got him.     -Alright. Where is he?
He's leaving Earth... Heading to Elysium.
Manuel! Rico! Get weapons! Let's get up there.
Echo leader 234, requesting landing in sector 22.
Roger that Echo leader 234. You are clear for entry...
-I see you got the G-1 there.     -Hey, back the fuck up!
-Or what?     -I'll let it go.
What you gonna do? Huh?
I want what's in your head, boy. Kill him!
Grab him, Deck!
What do you want us to do, ma'am?
I want everyone coming out of that vehicle apprehended by Homeland Security.
Evacuate everyone on the level five clearence out of the building, now.
I warned you of this.
An unlicenced vehicle just crashed potentially threatening the Torus.
All because of your inability to act. Evacuate him.
-Get your hands off me.     -This is an act of war.
That puts the CCB under my control.
Now, if you'll let me do my job.
I'm sure you have a fund raiser to attend.
Let's go, sir.
Max!
Take me out of here, Max!
I'm trying!
Air quality reaching toxic levels.
Get me out of here!
It is recommended you exit the craft immediately.
Run!
Fuck!
2 Illegals heading northeast in zone 3
You deal with those two. I'll handle this pussy.
Welcome to the spectacular properties from your...
Error
No!
No citizen detected.
Please she's sick, help us. She's gone into a coma.
Please!
Shouldn't we remove this thing?
Can't, till we get all the data.
It's wired into him neurologically.
The data is intact, yes?
Data looks intact.
Warning
We can still pull this data out of him, which will kill him.
Oh, it's fine.
How long before you can download and turn the system online?
Not long, Ma'am.
Keep everything in a restricted cloud. Lock down all access.
Starting prep right now.
And get these two out of here.
Roger that.
Kurt, you wanna go get the boss' chicks?
Yeah, good.
Give them the runaround.
Keep them busy.
Got him!
Let's go!
Alright. 50 exabytes, buddy. Are you ready?
What are you taking out of him?
Hey! What're you doing to him?
What's gonna happen to him? Hey!
Rise and shine.
-Get up!     -Max.
Max. Max. Max!
Get in there!
Yes. Boss got fucked up, eh?
Ate that fucking grenade, eh!
His brain is fine. But he's gonna be pissed when he wakes up.
Remember what cock-up happened in India when he lost his hat?
Kruger.
Boss?
It's Crowe.
Where is he?
All right, all set. Let's reach the data.
I got the needle prepped. You wanna grab this?
Grab the needle! Grab the needle! Grab the...
-Where did they take the girls?     -The Armory.
Where the fuck is that?
Level three.
Lethal radiation poisoning detected. You require urgent medical attention.
You idiot! Do you realize what you've done?
You crashed an unlicensed vehicle into a suburban area.
Your orders were to keep this covert.
Do you even remember what that means?
Have you completely lost your mind? You're useless to me.
If the administration realized what we're doing,
they'd hang us both for treason.
For God's sake, Kruger! Are you listening to me?
Yes.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm listening.
I'm sorry that we crashed the vehicle and ruined someone's lawn.
But nobody is gonna hang us for treason.
We do the hanging!
Put your hand on it, keep pressure on it.
How tough you be now, eh?
Right boys, Elysium is about to get its first proper president.
She needs some medical attention.
I was gonna heal your daughter.
But now, I'll make sure she's never healed.
Drakie, don't trust any of those politicians!
Clear out this whole building!
Thank you, boss.
I'm gonna find that little gangster.
I'm gonna take what's in his head. This place is mine now.
You want to come to my fucking house and play?
Let's play!
I'm going to annihilate that little motherfucker.
Hey!
What the hell was that?
All members of CCB please go to the nearest exit and proceed calmly to...
Go, go, go!
No.
Citizen deceased
Emergency systems are now online
Please follow indicated procedures
Spider!
Do you read me, Spider?
Max, where are you.
The thing in my head, it can make everyone a citizen here, right?
Yeah.
You know how to get it out, right?
Yes.
You're sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
OK, listen to me carefully.
Armory selected.
Set.
Turn me on.
OK.
Crowe, get rid of those two.
My pleasure, boss. My pleasure.
Where are you, Pikey? Where are you?
How is it, girl?
Let's play.
-Come on, I'll be nice. Gentle, I promise.     -No. Please.
-Come on.     -Get off me!
-Want me to hurt the girl?     -No.
Then come here.
Fuck!
She alive?
For now.
Stay behind me.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
I have a plan.
D'you hear that sound?
That's the sound of me coming for you.
I'll find you! I'll hunt you down!
Frey, we have to split up.
-What?     -Listen.
You're gonna go to the surface, OK? Take this.
Find a house, get her to a med-bay.
-Max, it won't work.     -Don't stop. Don't stop...
She doesn't have an ID. It doesn't work.
It will this time. I know how to fix it.
-Surface selected     -Go.
Come with me.
-I'm right behind you.     -No.
I promise.
OK, a mother and her daughter just went up in that elevator.
They're going to the surface headed for a med-bay.
Send one of your guys make sure they get there.
And we have our deal.
Right to a med-bay, man.
-Let's go.     -Let's go.
-Go, go, go!     -This way!
Hurry up, man.
...emergency lock down...
Almost there. Almost there.
What's that?
It's just a ... bitch!
That's what I'm talking about.
Fire has been detected...
Hold the door! Hold the door!
...have been shut down.
-Come on! Come on!     -Go, go, go
Let's go!
Fuck. C'mon!
Go! You first. C'mon!
Come on! Stand up!
Stand! Stand up! Come on!
Stand up!
You little fucker.
I'm gonna take your fucking head off!
Dude, you should definitely stand up now!
No!
Stay there.
Fuck!
-You think you could get through me?     -Come on, Max! Come on!
I'm just getting started.
Come on.
Don't give up now. Get up, come! Come on!
You want more than this? I know you.
You look a little bit dizzy, eh?
Did I get you?
Are you bleeding? You must get that looked at.
Hey, boy?
You wanna heal that little girl?
You just need to come through me.
You got some fire in you, boy.
You almost had me.
We die together, boy.
Come on, man, let's go.
Let's go, man, let's do it. Come on!
Ready? Let's go.
Get the guards, now!
Alright.
This'll do it.
Hurry.
OK, we're good, we're good.
We're good.
What?
Max.
It's OK. I know.
There's no coming back from this.
No med-bay can heal you.
Alright, give it to me.
Take it.
OK.
You just have to press that button.
Frey?
Max? Max where are you?
I'm gonna have to break my promise.
I can't make it back up there.
You remember what I said when we were kids?
Yes.
I'll take us there one day.
-Really?     -Yeah, I promise.
You wouldn't believe what I'm looking at right now.
Tell Matilda I really liked her story.
I figured out why the Hippo did it.
Come on!
You go first. Come on!
We all have something special, Max.
Something we're destined to do.
Something for which we were born.
Fuck you!
Let go of me!
Come on, please.
My baby. My dear.
Stand down, Officers.
Arrest him.
I can not arrest a citizen of Elysium.
What?
Doing a great job.
Guess who Elysium belongs to now?
See how beautiful it looks to us down here?
Now look how beautiful we look from up there.
Now it belongs to you.
So you'll never forget where you come from.
My little Max.
极  乐  世  界
21世纪末期地球上疾病肆虐 污染严重 人口极剧过剩
地球上最富有的居民 为了维持他们的生活方式 离开了这个星球
洛杉矶 , 2154年
洛杉矶市医院
安全漏洞 飞船密码报失
国民合作局
公民 C·查维兹 女性
检测到多重综合骨折
门故障
检测到器官组织
协议
核心更新 M·克鲁格特工 开除
协议重启 编译
序列完成
是否要保护数据
是
选择A-瘫痪 选择B-致死
致死
人脑上传准备就绪
卡莱尔 我来了
弹药编码
已填弹
阿姆达因公司
引爆
锁定目标
正在填弹
同步完成
协议重启
信号干扰
可能目标身份确认
麦克斯·达·科斯塔
信号干扰
接近警告 一艘无照飞船正在靠近
颅面复原
完成
公民资格授权   人口：非法移民   人口：合法公民
下载数据将导致载体死亡
系统重启
阿姆达因
核心更新
新公民 >>> 已增加
公民 玛蒂尔达·圣蒂亚歌
检测到急性淋巴细胞白血病
100%清除
新公民需要医疗救助
计算中...
派遣急救飞船去地球提供医疗服务
麦克斯！
快过来！
别让姐妹们等着
这是芙蕾
她也是新来的
你识字吗？
这是长颈鹿，是从非洲来的
是的
那里有很多机器仆人，从早到晚为你服务
如果你住在那里，你永远不会生病也不会变老
有一天我会带大家去那里
-真的吗？  -对，我保证
芙蕾和麦克斯
永远是朋友
麦克斯，你是不是又偷东西了？
太让我伤心了，你干吗要这样？
为了存钱吗？
你想有一天买张票去那里？
那里不是你能去的，我也是
但这不公平，嬷嬷
我为什么不能去？
有时候我们没法理解
我们只能接受这一切
但我知道一件事
我知道你很特别
有一天你会干一件大事
你就是为这而生的
我的小麦克斯
你好啊，伙计！
去上班啊，每天早起去流水线上工作
去让世界变得更好吗？
真是太好笑了，我得上班，太好笑了
得了，孩子！你觉得我有钱吗？
我看起来像有钱人吗？
那你呢，你有钱吗？
来吧，让我看看你有什么？
等一下
有五块钱，太好了，我有五块钱！我发财了
我终于能买张去极乐世界的船票了？
那是我的
请按次序排队，你们的车已经来了
我没带东西
检查过了，往前走
早上好，警官
大量犯罪前科，多项重罪，背包里是什么？
基本上都是美发工具
不，我逗你呢…
嘿…我是去上班，伙计，背包里什么也没有
行了，那是我的…
轻罪，不服从指挥
我只是去上班，伙计
-通过  -没东西，是吧？
零容忍政策适用于所有公民
没事了吧？
你要立即报告你的假释官
谢谢你，公民
不，谢谢你
芙蕾，二号床，骨折，谢谢
麦克斯？
芙蕾…
我还以为你在…
-什么时候回来的？  -我回来有一阵子了
-你好像没怎么变  -不，这次不是我的错
当然不是
-让我看看  -怎么样？
骨折很严重
你真的当上护士了！
是啊
真是太好了
你还在偷车吗？
不，天哪，我早就不干那些傻事了
我在阿姆达因工作，做流水线，从基层干起…
-芙蕾，三楼那边要你去  -马上就去
-现在既然你回来了…  -等一下
麦克斯，稍等
多明尼加，你能照顾一下这里吗？
嘿，听着，既然现在你回来了
麦克斯，对不起，我得走了
很高兴见到你，别惹麻烦了
我没有
听着…
我明白，我知道你为什么离开那里，我了解
如果我像你一样聪明，我也会闪人
一起吃晚饭吧，仅仅是…
要不喝咖啡也行
-不  -天哪
我得再弄断条胳膊，才能引起你的注意吗？
-别这样  -…我真会这么做
我的生活很复杂，麦克斯
我只是，我…我很想你
-我星期三晚上八点下班，行了吧？  -好的
-喝咖啡  -喝咖啡，很好
快走吧
所有假释犯必须通过武器核查
你好
开始之前，我想解释一下…
麦克斯·达·科斯塔，今天在34-B公共汽车站，违反了刑法第2219条
是的，我就是想跟你说这件事
这其实是个误会
假释期延长八个月
等等，什么？不，不，我能解释是怎么回事
我开了个玩笑，然后，你知道的…
不要再说了
警官记录了暴力和反社会行为
很遗憾必须延长假释期
检测到心率加快
-要吃颗药吗？  -不用了！
谢谢，我想解释一下…
不要再说了
性格分析显示会有78.3%的几率回复到旧的行为模式
偷窃高级车，用致命武器袭击
拒捕
-你想和人类谈谈吗？  -不，我没事，谢谢
-你的口气是在挖苦还是辱骂？  -没有
辱骂假释官是一项重罪
我知道
嘿，达·科斯塔！
-你上班迟到了  -对，伙计，我碰到点小麻烦…
不，不，这样不能工作，你走吧
不，不，我很好，伙计，我能工作
这没什么，这个等一下就能拆了，我没事了
-你没事？  -我没事！
好吧，那扣你半天工资
-好的，行吧  -能干这活算你运气好
没有检测到武器，你可以进入
请保持工作站的整洁
整洁的工作站才是有效率的工作站
快看啊，伙计，他好像长得像你
他的脸做过换肤手术了，看上去不错
注意：所有工人必须完成每周的指标
请向你的上级报告一切不安全行为
如果我们找不到方法提升股价
我们的投资者会对我们失去信心的
你觉得我跑到地球上来干什么？
你以为我喜欢呼吸这里的空气吗？
-不，当然了，不过…  -我能做的都已经做了…
就是为了让公司恢复营利
这公司还是我一手建立的
现在，我要失陪了
我没法再和你们谈下去了，谢谢
34号关闭！
34号点火
快给她做身份证！
快快快，我们时间不多了
三艘飞船已准备好了，蜘蛛
好的，放到荧幕上
密码通过了
启动飞船
我们要上去了！
-欢迎光临  -你好，夫人
-去看看花园吧  -我们会的，谢谢
-你好，德拉古夫人  -你好
天哪，都长这么大了
嗨，最近好吗？
-挺好的，孩子们都来了？  -对，和多明尼加在一起
我有份礼物要送给你，想看看吗？在沙龙里面
跟妈妈一起去拿吧
-在沙发边上  -太好了
再见
夫人，要不要提提神？
命令已经取消了
抱歉打扰您，夫人，我们发现有几艘无照飞船入境
午安，国防部长德拉古
三级警报三艘无照飞船正在靠近极乐世界领空
六号，七号紧急命令生效
22/B39号协议正在运行
注意外来飞船
你们未经许可擅自进入极乐世界领空
-爸爸！  -没事的！
立即回到地球，否则我们将采取行动
你们违反了极乐世界的规定
普通警告没有用
距离我们一万五千公里，还在靠近…
-我们该怎么办，夫人？  -启动克鲁格
夫人，根据355号行政命令，我们没被授权启用地球上的资产
我正在授权给你
是，夫人
特工32A，数据包发给你了
欢迎，克鲁格特工！
他们距离我们一万公里，还在靠近
发送飞船坐标
同步目标数据
把他们打下来！
批准执行，21-B，批准执行
导弹已发射！
见鬼
侦测到导弹锁定，弹着预备，十…
八…七…六…
五…四…三…
二…一…
击毁两艘飞船，共有四十六人死亡
导弹五秒后到达…
-最后一枚导弹没打中  -真可笑！
只有一艘进去了
夫人，飞船已经冲进我们的大气层
第一艘无照飞船着陆了
把那艘船上所有的人都给我抓起来
身份确认
扫瞄
启动重建程序
不！
我们逮捕了32人，13人死亡，还有两个非法移民在逃，夫人
身体重建完成
你们因触犯68-C移民法案被逮捕！
-所有非法移民已被拘捕，夫人  -好的
送他们去驱逐部
德拉古部长，请立即向帕特尔总统汇报
德拉古部长，请向帕特尔总统汇报
你好，伙计？怎么了？
跟平常一样，因为警察
-你没事吧？  -没事，不用担心
麦克斯，我跟你说件事，听着…
-不！  -什么‘不’？
你都没听我说完呢
-行了，说吧  -好的
你知道山上洛斯齐塔斯的房子吗？
知道，他们有很多枪
是的，他们有五辆车，都是新的
我们三个去，明天午饭的时候
-午饭的时候  -就这计划？
我的天哪
-你有更好的主意吗？  -对，我们带上一个人
太阳出来前就去，你们偷那两辆最快的车
把另几辆车的电池
你耍我，去死吧！
你上当了！
求求你，伙计，你是最棒的，给我一年，就一年
-我不想再回监狱了  -就一年，求求你！
看看你，你以前是传奇人物，现在呢？
现在时间上午5点50分
没有检测到武器，你可以进入
34号关门！
注意，门没对齐，工人将会…
嘿，你拖慢进度了
不，我的机器卡住了！
注意:工人们每班上洗手间不能超过一次…
-你干了什么？达·科斯塔？  -没有，我只是让门重新启动
让我看看
-挤到栈板了  -对，位置动了
-你进去  -不，我是说…
听着，要嘛你现在进去…
要嘛我找其他人，然后你就卷铺盖走人
-拜托，伙计  -不，不，我没开玩笑，懂吗？
快进去！
快点，伙计们，快回去工作！
见鬼
不，不，不，停下！
嘿！
嘿，快走开，危险！
太晚了！
把他弄出来！
我有一个梦想，嬷嬷
我只是想住在那里
从我们这里看那里很美是吧？
是的
好，现在…
从那里看我们这里也很美
留着吧
现在是你的了
永远不要忘了你是从哪里来的
出了什么事？
你受到了致命剂量的辐射
你的器官将会严重衰竭
五天后你就会死
出了什么事？为什么停工？
-他被辐射了  -别朝我呼气
-把嘴捂上  -对不起，先生
他的皮肤脱落吗？还是什么？
我可不想把床换掉，快把他弄出去
-是，先生  -好，谢谢
卡莱尔先生，您的飞船准备出发了
请签名接受药物治疗
米珀洛，超强效
能在你死前维持器官正常运作
每顿饭吃一粒
感谢你的服务
昨天下午三点你击落两艘飞船，杀死了四十六个平民
你处理非法移民应该尽可能低调
我已经意识到了
另外你使用的这个…特工
M·克鲁格先生
有十五次侵犯人权…
强奸、绑架、刑求逼供
这个人已经被确诊有严重心理问题
我们已经明确告诉过你，我们不再用潜伏的特工了
跟我说说，帕特尔总统
你有孩子吗？
接受审查的是你不是我
那我假设你没有
如果你有孩子
也许你会表现得更有益于…
延长我们这个地方的使用寿命
我的想法和做法现在已经过时了
这我心里很清楚
但是当他们来到你家…
你为你的孩子建造的家…
和你孩子的孩子…
靠公关和竞选承诺是赶不走那些人的
只能靠我！
我听够了！这是最后的警告
如果你再自作主张行动，你就会被解职
让我们永久性地开除克鲁格特工吧
全都赞成？
很好，立即生效
来点啤酒吗？
你已经被国民合作局开除了
请去当地大使馆退还所有武器
该死的政治！去死吧！
等我一下…
麦克斯…
麦克斯！
你怎么了？发生什么事？
天哪，我来帮你，进屋去吧
麦克斯，怎么回事？
-麦克斯，怎么回事？  -我不该进去的
到哪去？
我受到致命剂量的辐射
致命剂量
你会好起来的，我来帮你
-你会好起来的，麦克斯  -他们给了我米珀洛
他们给了我该死的…米珀洛
我只有五天可活了！只有五天！
你得把药吃了
-极乐世界能治这病  -我知道
-我要去见蜘蛛  -麦克斯，麦克斯！
先把药吃了！
给你水！
去见蜘蛛，你需要钱
就算我把所有积蓄都给你，也买不起一张票
他会给我一张票
他会给我一张该死的票的
芙蕾，你知道我们已经尽全力救你女儿了
今天我和委员会讨论过了
他们建议把你女儿送回家
她在家里我怎么还能在这里工作？
她随时可能发作，费萨尔医生
我知道，如果她又发作了，你就把她带回来住院，这没问题
但她现在不能住院
这里不是极乐世界，我们没法治好她
麦克斯！
好久不见啊，哥们！
工厂那边怎么样啊？
-我要请你帮个忙  -什么？我没听见，什么？
我要一张上去的票，和一个身份证
行，当然可以
位子要靠窗的还是靠道的？
我没跟你开玩笑
听着，我会回来的，我会回来为你工作
你要什么都行，我一定会还你的
知道吗？
这个…可是…
无价的
这个是无价的
我问你个问题
你知道每天有多少笨蛋
跑到这里来，说跟你同样的话吗？
说什么我有个小孩，他们每天都来
麦克斯，如果我是你，我就马上离开这里，懂吗？
麦克斯，不…
麦克斯，不要…
我为了你坐了三年牢
就凭我为你，做的那些事，你就该送我上去
-感觉到了吗？  -来吧，杀了我
现在我身体里都是辐射物
要是溅出来还会辐射到你
-你真的要死了吗？  -我要死了，混蛋，听见了吗？
看见吗？结束了，把枪放下
把枪放下！把枪放下！都滚出去！
听到吗？
听着，我在找人帮我做一件事
但是我这里没人有那个胆量
你说叫你干什么都行，对吗？
麦克斯…
-没事吧？  -我没事
这个…
我的朋友
这个就是你上去的票
你最后为我做件事，我就送你上去
什么事？
一个极乐世界的混蛋，懂吗？
一个亿万富翁，他下到地球上来做生意…
他来…他来…管他来干什么，我们绑架他
-得了！  -放松
我的计划比你想的复杂
我们不要他的表，不要他的车，这些东西都不要
这个，我们要这个
我们要他脑袋里的那些有机信息
我说的是银行代码、密码、登陆数据…
靠这些能拿几亿的钱
你要做的就是接通他的大脑，用这东西把数据下载到你的脑子里
然后带回来给我
这太疯狂了，麦克斯
我们一旦核实了数据，我就给你一张免费的单程票
还附送饮料和小吃
到时候你只要走进一间屋子，运行医疗机，你就痊愈了
桑德罗会负责手术，你认识他吗？
-怎么回事…  -我的天哪！
我没事
事实上你看上去虚弱
虚弱得一塌糊涂，所以…
知道吗，我会让他们…
这太疯狂了，我们走吧，听我的
我还能怎么办？
我会让他们给你装上这个…
…这是！
第三代外骨盔甲
它会和神经系统连接，让你和机器人一样强
准备好做手术了，对吗？
我们快走吧，拜托
我要一个四人团队，人我来选
我会派我自己的数据师去
脑对脑数据传输很难搞的
不过我要带上胡力欧，你也要给他一张上去的票，跟我一样
好，没问题
好了，我去叫他们过来
等等！
目标得是约翰·卡莱尔
你说的是阿姆达因公司的执行总裁？
对，就是他
德拉古部长，卡莱尔先生来了
你来这里是想说服我续签和阿姆达因的合同吧？
你总是这么聪明
跟我来
我对你那些小想法不感兴趣
我感兴趣的是更大的东西
这个地方在死去
它的内部得了一种政治病，这颗肿瘤必须铲除掉
你和你的公司，你们的营利越来越少
是…
你造了这个圆环
你能不能重置伺服器，扶植一位新总统上台？
这是政变吗？
你的意思是要政变？
有可能吗？
我可以写个重启序列？
关掉整个系统到那个时候…
你就能编码一位新总统了
这就是你要做的事？
如果成功，你们公司就能续签两百年的合同
导弹防御系统、机器人一切用来保护我们自由的东西
你们的新总统，会保证这一切的
你有工作了！卡莱尔先生
就是这个人
-就是他吗？  -就是他
坐下
我们会切开你的头
温柔点，桑德罗，温柔点
先给他弄个身份证
我们先给他弄个身份证
-是这个吗？  -对，准备好
手抬起来
我们只有这个
你找到什么？
这会连接你的DNA
你会融入那里，就像你是生在那里的
该动真格的了
伙计
嘿
这会疼吗？
对，小妞，会有点疼
不过也很爽
手术结束你就会变成贫民区的忍者了
玛丽安娜！…把骨锯拿下来
我什么也听不见，快把骨锯拿下来！
你不会弄死我吧？
不会有事的，老兄
麦克斯
我在这里
我们能成功
是的！
嘿！
他醒了！
你挺过来了？
真没想到！
你还能打手枪呢？
情况怎么样？
他现在很强了？
你对我做了什么？
给了你一条活路
见鬼
你好，搭档？
这套装备感觉怎么样？
感觉棒极了！
给我看
给你
这是什么，传家宝吗？
等一下
这是空爆弹
你选定目标…
子弹会在目标周围爆炸，杀伤半径五米
还有…
这玩意还配了同步爆破弹
不错啊
行动吧！
先生…
飞船准备好了
能听见吗？
收到
计划是这样的
我们在工厂外面等他的飞船起飞
你发一枚爆破弹上去
然后赶到坠毁地点拿数据
好的，明白
好了，开始行动吧！上吧！
你紧张吗？
-不！  -不？
我都吓得尿裤子了
-我们不会死在这里的  -对
上，上，上！
十五秒后将加速到超声速
快点，快点，快点！
发动机严重损坏
一位极乐世界公民在地球遇到危险
马上显示资料…
公民身份确认，约翰·卡莱尔，N8321P…
我看见你了，混蛋！
我这里出了点事
克鲁格，能听到吗？
德拉古小姐，很高兴听到你的声音
有个携带敏感大脑数据的公民在城外
几个小偷想抢劫那些数据
什么数据？
这是机密
你才不会叫一个刚被开除的特工去帮你找什么该死的机密数据呢
政府不知道这件事，对吗？
我想要什么都行，对吗？
请做好防撞击准备
请保持冷静，你承受的损伤为零
真是个好消息啊
我有一个条件，我干这工作，你得帮我复职
好的
我帮你安排了你喜欢的特工
当然了，完全是保密的，他们马上就会赶到你那边
把任务资料发给我
走吧，伙计们，快出来！
机器人，那边有几辆某种型号的车，上面有一个…
有两个人
他们都带着武器，我要他们死
机器人！
枪卡弹了！
身份确认：麦克斯·达·科斯塔，联邦假释号61492-8-557
好了！
它在填弹！
-没事吧！我们快走，我去开门  -快走，我掩护你们！
快，快，快！
别乱动
拿过来！
那边还有一个！
去死吧，混蛋！
别打目标！
不，不！他中弹了！
公民受到心胸外伤
血压正在下降
伤口不在头上？
-他还有气吗？  -有，伤口在胸上
那我们还能工作，帮我托住他的头
把这个插到你身上，快点
来吧，宝贝，快点！
-好  -有反应吗？
对，我们在同步
你不知道，自己在做什么
距离目标一分钟，长官
行了，同步上了，来吧，宝贝，传吧
我说能行吧
发生数据抢劫，他们正在下载，已经在传了
伙计们，有人来了
该死的！
快点，伙计们，快点
那是雷文机，是军用飞机
-就快好了，百分之97…98  -快点，他们来了
-马上就好  -99！
搞定，成功了！
见鬼！天哪，数据被破坏了！
等等，等一下
我没法读数据，是乱码！读不出
什么？
-快点，伙计们，我们得走了  -‘乱码’是什么东东？
该死的！
不，不！我们再运行一次！
-放开我，伙计！我放弃了  -求求你，再运行一次
去你的！快点，我们离开这里
你要去哪里，桑德罗？
快离开这里！该死的！
快走，伙计
快离开那里！
快走！我们快走！
老大，有个逃跑的
开火！
这才是我说的那码子事！
见鬼！
目标朝南-西南方向移动
快点，麦克斯！它来了！
我们找到另一个
好了！
这计划错了！彻底糟透了，伙计！
保持盘旋状态！
我看你往哪里跑？
来吧！
见鬼！
该死的！
来吧！
不！
不，不
不！起来！
起来！
不！
一名袭击者步行逃走了，夫人
他们有数据，重复：
那些小偷抢了数据
不惜一切代价逮捕目标，不要毁坏他的大脑
我们走！有一个跑了！
公民死于失血过多导致的心跳停止
死亡时间17点45分
出来，你躲去哪里了？
那是什么？
看上去像是一群猪，老大
该死的！找到他！
送我们回坠机地点，看看他们留下什么？
明白
谢谢
老大，你最好过来看看这个
这是我们扫瞄到的罪犯
和卡莱尔之间传输资料的记录
怪不得她那么着急
那家伙的脑袋里有打开王国的钥匙！
我们要找到他
我派姑娘们出去
搜寻网路3到11
我授权了全面封锁
把洛杉矶定为禁飞区
-整个洛杉矶吗？  -凶手还逍遥法外
逮捕到他之前，不许有任何人离开那座城
搞什么…？
麦克斯
-嗨，亲爱的！  -嗨
我们可以回家了
我的病好了吗？
我去开车，好吗？
我马上就回来
芙蕾…
麦克斯！
我的天哪，你怎么了？
-见鬼，我去叫医生  -不，不！
-我不能进去  -麦克斯！
-我不能进去…  -麦克斯，听我说，你得看医生，明白吗？
有人在找我，他们要杀我
-我来这里是找你的，我需要你帮忙  -麦克斯！
接受治疗得走系统程序
求你救救我，我不想死
麦克斯！
别睡着！
-我想看看那个人  -妈妈会救他的，好吗？
你快睡觉
别睡着！
你实在是太重了，麦克斯，帮帮我！
起来！
麦克斯，你行的！
别睡着，翻个身！
麦克斯，麦克斯，等等
-谢谢  -谁把你弄成这样的？
我不知道，我…我工作时受伤了
我只好去帮蜘蛛工作，这样才能到上面去治病
但事情搞糟了，我麻烦大了
妈妈？
宝贝，过来！
这人是谁？
他叫麦克斯，妈妈跟你一样大时就认识他了
-这是玛蒂尔达  -嗨！
你去看动画片吧，好吗？
我一会就来
我不知道你有…对不起，我该走了
-等等，麦克斯，等等，你不能走  -我不该来的，我得离开了
麦克斯！她快死了，她已经到了白血病晚期
我说过我的生活很复杂，我需要你帮我
-但我不知道该怎么做  -做什么？
-带她去极乐世界  -我帮不了她，我…
如果可以我一定会的
那这个呢，假公民身份，如果你带她上去
-能用这个帮她治病吗？  -那样没用的
这是我的编码，是跟我的DNA锁定的
那些找我的人，他们是…你不明白这些人是谁
一旦他们找到我，会把我们全都杀了
我唯一能帮你的就是离开这里，我向你发誓
-她是我的一切  -对不起
你身上绑着绷带
对，我绑着绷带
你在干什么？
我不希望你生病，你想听故事吗？
什么，不…
很久以前有一只猫鼬住在丛林里
它肚子很饿，但它太小了
非常小
其他大的动物都有食物吃，因为它们能摘到水果
于是它去和一只河马交朋友
行了，别说了！
这只猫鼬结局很惨吧？
不，不是这样的，因为它可以站在河马的背上
摘到所有它想要的水果
-河马有什么好处呢？  -河马想要一个朋友
对不起
老大
找到他了
马上着陆
-妈妈，出什么事了吗？  -没事的，宝贝
安全！
这是什么？
午安
很抱歉突然闯进你家，这并不意味着…
我不是故意要吓到你的小女儿的
我和我的手下是来这里找一位先生…
他不久前就在这房子里
希望你能告诉我们他去哪里了
不
我…
-我不知道他去哪里了  -我不喜欢…
…在孩子面前使用暴力
所以我要请你闭上眼睛，亲爱的
-没事的，宝贝  -我真的需要你告诉我
嘿？
-想起来了吗？  -妈妈！
闭上眼睛，把你该死的眼睛闭上
让她闭上眼睛
求求你，我不知道他在哪里
他受伤了，我救了他，然后他走了
求求你！
你瞧瞧，这年头都没人讲义气了？
那是什么？
-你这里开了个医院吗？  -她生病了
她生病了吗？让我看看她…行吗？
-别碰她  -看见吗？这是保护的本能！
我说了不要碰她！
我只是想跟她说几句话
不要碰她！
-带上她，来吧！  -你要带我们去哪里？
-我有你想要的东西  -别害怕，宝贝
没事的，宝贝
给我坐下！闭上嘴！
站住！
不，不，别杀他！把枪放下！让他过来！
-你拿到了什么东西，对吗？  -什么？
所以他们会封锁领空…为了什么？
银行电汇？军事情报？一定是什么重要的东西！
没有，我什么也没弄到！
全都是乱码，胡力欧死了，你欠我个人情，我们快去上面吧！
去不了！他们干扰了飞行系统信号！
没有人能上得去
-什么时候能恢复？  -我怎么知道？
-我一定要到上面去！  -所有人都要到上面去
我的人在想办法
看是不是能有机会上线
不过，现在呢…
让我先看看你脑袋里的东西
别碰我，伙计！
看着我，如果他们封锁整个领空
只是为了你脑袋里的东西…
那么让他们开放领空的钥匙可能也在那里面，对吗？
来吧
好了
为了这个，他们追到天边也要抓到你
这是什么？
这是极乐世界的重启程序
谁拥有了这个，就能改写极乐世界的整个系统
开放边界…
让所有人都成为极乐世界的公民
这东西能救你的命
-能救所有人  -我什么时候能走？
我的人想混进去关掉信号干扰，应该很快能搞定…
-别扯淡了，我们什么时候能走？  -我不知道
五天吧…一周？
见鬼去吧，我根本活不了五天！我只能活几个小时
我的人在努力
你总是在努力，但总是没办法送我上去
我都不明白，你干吗要想办法送人上去？
他们只会被打死
但有了那个就不同了，情况不一样了！
我们能控制系统，我们能说了算！
我们能彻底改变这该死的历史了！
回到刚才说的
我脑子里的东西对他们来说很重要，对吗？
不要这样
如果它落到坏人手里，他们会把我们永远隔绝在外
听着，伙计，我现在就要上去
如果你能找到我，我也治好了病，我就把东西都给你
-我不想死在这里  -你这样不对，麦克斯，别这样
别开枪！别开枪！
没事的，没事的
我一直想找个老婆
但就是一直没法安定下来，你知道的？诱惑太多了
可是你…
你让我想要安定下来
你真的让我想安定下来，宝贝
-该死的，长官  -什么？
你最好过来看看
-干吗？怎么回事？  -看看这该死的橡树
带我们下去
-接着  -是的，长官
把门打开
别过来，你们得照我说的做
否则我把自己脑袋炸了，明白吗？
好的！
我脑袋里的东西都能给你！
只要你带我上去，给我用医疗机
-我掌握的东西很有价值  -我们能帮你治疗
给你用医疗机，这些问题都能解决
走吧！我们带你上去
上面天气不错，空气又好又干净，你会喜欢那里的
-别想动歪脑筋！  -上来吧！
见见我的弟兄，来吧！
别害羞，他们不会伤害你的
我来给你介绍，这位是德雷克，这是麦克斯
你好，猛男？
我们走！
是的，夫人，我们已经逮捕了目标
-打开领空，我们要回家了  -我们十九分钟后见
-取消禁飞区  -是，夫人
等等…
等一下，那是什么？…
网络恢复了吗？马塞罗！这是怎么回事？恢复了吗？
我们连上线了，蜘蛛
芙蕾…
对不起，我会搞定的
-我们找到他了  -好的，他在哪里？
他在离开地球…去极乐世界
曼纽尔！黎戈！带上武器！我们到上面去
EL234请求在22区着陆
收到，EL234，批准你们进入
-我看到你有G-1手雷  -行了，给我退后
-要不然呢？  -我就引爆它
你想怎么样？
我要你脑袋里的东西，孩子，杀死他！
抓住他！
我们要怎么做，夫人？
我要国土安全局逮捕所有从里面走出来的人
把安全许可级别在五级以下的人全部清出这栋楼
我警告过你的
刚才一艘无照的飞船坠毁了，对这里是潜在的威胁
会发生这种事都是因为你的无能，带他出去
-别碰我  -这属于战争行为
这种情况下国民合作局由我来控制
现在我要去工作了
我肯定你要去参加一个筹款活动
走吧，先生
麦克斯！
快帮我下来，麦克斯！
我在想办法！
空气质量达到中毒状态
快帮我下来！
建议您立即离开这艘飞船
快跑！
见鬼！
两个非法移民在第三区朝东北方去
你去抓那两个，我来对付这个混蛋
欢迎参观这栋壮观的豪宅，它占地…
错误
不要啊！
未探测到公民
求求你，她生病了，帮帮我们，她已经昏迷了
求求你！
我们是不是该弄掉这些东西？
不行，我们得先弄到数据
这和他的神经系统连在一起
数据没有受损吧？
看上去是的
警告
我们可以把数据取出来，不过他会死
无所谓了
你们下载数据，让系统恢复正常要多长时间？
不用很久，夫人
所有资料都保留在机密云里，禁止一切访问
马上开始准备
把那两个弄走
明白
科特，想去抓老大的女人吗？
好的，伙计
采取机动回避
让他们白忙一场
找到了！
我们走！
行了，50位元组，哥们，准备好了吗？
你要从他身上拿什么？
你想对他干什么？
他会怎么样？
该起床了
-起来！  -麦克斯
麦克斯，麦克斯，麦克斯！
给我进去！
是的，老大搞砸了，呃？
吃了个该死的手雷，呃！
他的大脑没事，不过他醒过来一定会气疯的
还记得上次他在印度掉了条胳膊吗？
克鲁格
老大？
我是克洛
他在哪里？
行了，准备好了，再打次镇静剂
准备好注射器，你抓住这个？
抓住针头！抓住针头！抓住…
-他们把姑娘们带哪里去了？  -去军械库了
那地方在哪里？
在第三层
检测到致命放射性中毒，你需要立即接受治疗
你这个笨蛋！知道自己干了什么吗？
你在城郊撞毁了一艘无照飞船
我给你的命令是秘密行动
你还记得这是什么意思吗？
你是不是疯了？你现在已经没用了
如果政府意识到我们在做什么
会以叛国罪把我们吊死
看在上帝的份上，克鲁格！你在听我说话吗？
是的
是的，夫人
我在听
很抱歉，我们的飞船坠毁弄坏了那些车辆和人家的草坪
没人能以叛国罪吊死我们
现在我们说了算！
把手放在上面，用力压住
你现在很难受了吧？
好了，孩子们！极乐世界终于要有个称职的总统了
她需要医疗
我本来想治好你女儿的
不过，现在我要确保她永远不会被治好
德雷克，永远别信政治家说的话！
把这栋楼清干净！
谢谢，老大
我要找到那个小流氓
拿到他脑袋里的东西，这里现在是我的了
你敢跑到我家里来玩！
那就玩吧！
我要干掉那个小混蛋
嘿！
这是怎么回事？
所有国民合作局的人员，请从最近的出口离开，冷静地前往底层…
快点，快走！
不
不用
公民死亡
现在启动紧急系统
请根据指示行动
蜘蛛！
你能听到吗？
麦克斯，你在哪里？
我脑袋里的东西，能让所有人成为这里的公民，对吗？
对
你知道怎么把它弄出来，对吗？
你确定吗？
是的，我确定
好，你仔细听我说
已选择军械库
好了
帮我启动
克洛，把那两个处理掉
乐意效劳，老大，乐意效劳
你在哪里？小子，你在哪里？
你好啊，小妞？
玩玩吧
-来吧，我会很好，很温柔的，我保证  -不，求求你
-来吧  -离我远点！
-你希望我伤害这个姑娘吗？  -不！
那就给我过来
见鬼！
她还活着吗？
目前还活着
待在我后面
我带你们出去
我有个计划
你听到这声音吗？
这是我来找你的声音
我会找到你！我会宰了你！
芙蕾，我们得分头行动
-什么？  -听着
你到地面上去，行吗？拿着这个
找个房子，给她用医疗机
-不，没用的  -别停下，别停下…
她没有身份证，没法用医疗机
这次一定能行，我有办法搞定
-已选择地面  -快去
跟我一起走
-我一会就来  -不
我保证
有个妈妈带着女儿刚才进了那边的电梯
她们要到地面上去找医疗机
你派个人护送她们到那里
我就履行诺言
直接去医疗机
-我们走  -快走
-快走，快点！  -过来这边！
快点伙计
…启动紧急封锁…
快到了，快到了
怎么啦？
只不过是点…皮肉伤！
这样才像话嘛
侦测到火灾…
离开门！离开门！
…门都已经关闭
-开了！快走！  -快快快
我们快走
该死的门！快开
快！你先走，快点！
快起来！站起来！
快起来！快起来！快点！
快起来！
你这个臭杂种
我要把你该死的头拧下来！
伙计，你现在一定要站起来！
不！
待在这里
见鬼！
-你以为你能打败我吗？  -加油，麦克斯！加油！
我才刚开始呢
起来
别这么快就放弃，起来！快点！
你不止这点本事？我知道的
你是不是有点头晕啊？
我划伤你了吗？
你在流血，你得去看医生
伙计？
你想治好那个小女孩？
你得先过我这关
你小子还有点本事的
你差点打败我
我们同归于尽吧
好了，我们快走
我们快去吧，快！
准备好了？我们走吧
别让门关上！
行了
来干吧
快点
可以开始了，可以开始了
可以开始了
什么？
麦克斯
没关系，我知道
无法再回头了
医疗机也治不好
行了，把键盘给我
拿着
好
你只要按那个按钮
芙蕾？
麦克斯？麦克斯你在哪里？
我没法实现我的承诺了
我到不了你那边了
记得我们小时候我说的话吗？
记得
有一天我会带大家去那里
-真的吗？  -是的，我保证
你不会相信我现在看到了什么？
告诉玛蒂尔达，我很喜欢她讲的故事
我明白了为什么河马会这么做
来吧！
你先来，来啊！
每个人都有自己的才能，麦克斯
一件他们注定要做的事
一件他们为之而生的事
去死吧！
放开我！
快点，求求你
我的宝贝，我亲爱的
解除战备，警官
逮捕他
我不能逮捕极乐世界的公民
什么？
伙计，干得好
猜猜极乐世界现在归谁了？
从我们这里看那里很美是吗？
从那里看我们这里也很美
现在是你的了
永远不要忘了你是从哪里来的
我的小麦克斯
字
字幕
字幕制
字幕制作
字幕制作 ★
字幕制作 ★ 至
字幕制作 ★ 至宏
字幕制作 ★ 至宏上
字幕制作 ★ 至宏上人